佩妮
Penny?
亲爱的  怎么了
Sweetheart, what's wrong?
他们为什么把这些可怕的东西放到网上
Why are they putting these awful things online?
艾利克斯·柯克曼之死
是交通事故还是认为谋杀？
柯克曼总统是否一手策划了他妻子的死亡？
亲爱的  我不知道  过来  过来
Honey, I don't know. Come here, come here.
- 他们说你杀了妈妈  - 哦
- They're saying you killed Mom. - Oh.
亲爱的  没人相信
Honey, nobody believes that.
他们就是故意刻薄  来抱抱
They're just being mean. Come here.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
今天感觉不好吗
Is it bad today?
非处方止痛药吗  我还不如去玩撞柱游戏呢
Over-the-counter pain relievers? I might as well be popping Skittles.
我讨厌就这样离开你
I hate leaving you like this.
- 嗯  我知道  - 我在做一些调查
- Mmm-hmm. I know. - I've been doing some research.
找个戒瘾陪护怎么样
What about arranging for a sober companion?
保姆吗  不了  谢谢你
A babysitter? No, thank you.
我们有资源  有选择  有解决方案
We have resources. There are options, solutions.
这些都不包括你辞职是吗
Aside from you quitting your job?
这就是你想问的吗
Is that really what you're asking?
对于有些妻子来说  有些丈夫不需要被要求
Some wives would. Some husbands wouldn't have to be asked.
我现在不能谈这个
I can't get into this right now.
想想找人来帮忙吧
Just think about bringing somebody in to help.
如果你需要我  给我打电话
Call me if you need me.
总统和美国人民一样
The president is laser-focused on the issues,
都把注意力集中在这些问题上
as are the American people,
而不是那些出现在丑陋网络上的肮脏垃圾
not on the vile garbage that washes up on the ugly Net.
听着  我得再接一个电话
Look, I've gotta take another call.
妈妈  怎么了
Hey, Mom, what's going on?
我在医院
I'm in the hospital.
什么  怎么回事儿
What? What happened?
很明显  我身上有个血块  所以他们要留我几天
Evidently, I have a blood clot, so they're keeping me a few days.
天啊  你为什么不早点给我打电话
Jesus! Why didn't you call me sooner?
- 我知道你有多忙  - 妈妈  别这样
- I know how stretched thin you are. - Mom, stop.
- 他们告诉你病因是什么了吗  - 他们没说
- Did they tell you what caused it? - They haven't said.
他们没说或者你没问他们吗
They haven't said or you haven't asked them?
我不喜欢麻烦别人
I don't like bothering people.
那我就喜欢了吗
And I do?
可那是你的工作
It's your job.
我早上可以到那儿
I can be there in the morning.
我会麻烦他们的  因为我就是干这个的
And I will bother them, since I'm such a pro.
但是你明天有场辩论
But you have the debate tomorrow.
是的  在奥兰多  只有几个小时的路程
Yeah, in Orlando. It's only a couple of hours away.
你没必要  亲爱的
You don't have to, honey.
妈妈  我会来的  我爱你  再见
Mom, I'm coming. I love you. Goodbye.
下一位嘉宾是国家安全顾问
Our next guest is national security advisor
兼副总统候选人亚伦·肖尔
and vice-presidential candidate, Aaron Shore,
你们很多人都知道他的另一个头衔
who many of you also know by his other title,
华盛顿特区的钻石王老五
DC's most eligible bachelor.
非常感谢  这是我的荣幸
Thank you very much. It's my pleasure.
第一场总统辩论将于明晚举行
The first presidential debate is tomorrow night.
您帮柯克曼总统准备对外经济政策了吗
Have you been helping prep President Kirkman on foreign policy?
当涉及到外交或国内事务
The president doesn't need my or anyone else's help
总统不需要我或任何人的帮助
when it comes to foreign or domestic affairs.
我们非常期待您的收看
We're certainly looking forward to tuning in.
我们猜测您会和您现在的同居女友
We assume you'll be attending
伊莎贝尔·帕尔多一起出席
with your now live-in girlfriend, Isabel Pardo.
是的  我们会一起去
Yes, we'll be there together.
- 第一次和某人同居吗  - 是的
- First time living with someone? - It is.
这是不是一种调整  不要忘记把厕所座圈放下来
Has it been an adjustment, remembering to put the toilet seat down?
你记得吗
You are remembering?
我正在努力  但我相信人们对柯克曼总统
I'm managing to, but I'm sure that people are more interested
明天晚上提出的愿景更感兴趣
in the vision President Kirkman will put forward tomorrow night.
当然  但是如果我不去问关于求婚的传闻
Of course, but our viewers would kill me
我们的观众会杀了我的
if I didn't ask about this rumor of a marriage proposal.
我们现在都在关注选举
Well, we're all focused on the election now,
以及柯克曼总统明智的中间派议程
and President Kirkman's sensible centrist agenda.
所以  没有求婚吗
So, no proposal?
只有明天晚上人们收听的柯克曼总统
Only that people tune in tomorrow night to hear the exciting plans
对未来四年的激动人心的计划
President Kirkman has for the next four years.
他们说我谋杀了我的妻子
They're saying that I had my wife murdered!
亚历克斯是俄罗斯间谍吗
That Alex was a Russian spy?
这是历史最低点  鉴于我们的政治已经变得
This is an all-time low, and that's saying a lot,
如此有害  如此腐败  这说明了很多问题
given the fact that our politics have become so poisonous, so rancid.
我不敢相信莫斯会堕落到这个地步
I can't believe Moss would stoop this low.
我们不要妄下结论  这可能只是一些疯狂的极端分子
Let's not jump to conclusions. This could be just some crackpot wing nut.
莫斯还没有发表声明
Moss hasn't released a statement yet.
这和纵容它一样糟糕  波特的团队立即做出了谴责
Which is as bad as condoning it. Porter's team condemned it right away.
他们认为我们应该对阿尔茨海默氏症的泄露负责
They think we're responsible for the Alzheimer's leak.
也许是这样  但也有一线希望
Possibly, yes, but there is a silver lining.
更多的选民会同情你  而不是相信这荒唐的废话
More voters are gonna sympathize with you than believe this ludicrous bullshit.
这事没有希望  这是对任何体面事物的侮辱
There is no silver lining to this crap. It's an affront to anything decent.
那就说出来  这个国家的所有
Then say that. I'm getting asked
主要新闻机构都要求我发表官方声明
by every major news outlet in this country for an official statement.
不  我不会用回复来强调这一点
No, I'm not gonna dignify this with a response.
别再给我讲每次我们被攻击时该如何报复了
And spare me the lecture on how we need to retaliate every time we're attacked.
我们没有给它任何喘息的机会
We're not giving this any oxygen.
政府什么也没说  竞选活动方什么也没说
The administration says nothing. The campaign says nothing.
懂了吗
Understood?
明白  先生
Understood, sir.
谢谢你  总统先生  我们走吧
Thank you, Mr. President.  Let's go.
第三季   第五集
指定
幸存者
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
精校
压制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
当你在吃东西的时候  让我们回顾一下我们所知道的
While you're stuffing your face, let's review what we know.
在多伦多诊所感染了流感的女性
The women who were infected with the flu at the Toronto clinic,
都接受了这名男护士的注射  很明显
they all received an injection from this male nurse,
这个人现在消失无踪了
who's obviously in the wind.
但是公寓小区里没人提到注射
But no one at the apartment complex mentions an injection,
那么他们是怎么得病的呢
so how did they get sick?
污染水  雾化
Tainted water, aerosolized.
通风口吗  空调系统
The vents? The HVAC system.
我们得回去把监控录像拿出来
We'll have to go back there and pull the security footage.
当然  是在你吃完死亡拼盘之后
After you finish your death plate, of course,
希望是在你噎死之前
and, hopefully, before your infarction.
这些人都非常值得总统的赦免
These people are all eminently deserving of presidential pardons.
毫无疑问  这是我们在选举年所追求的
Inarguable is what we're looking for in an election year.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
即便美国总统输了  他不会输的
If POTUS loses, which he won't,
我们只有几个月的时间来完成这件事
we're only gonna have a couple of months to get this done.
我准备备份每个案子
I'm prepared to back up every case.
这正是我选你来打头的原因
Which is precisely why I selected you to spearhead this.
你可是真枪实干的
You're no bullshit,
所以我知道你能把这些名字都备份起来
so I knew you were gonna be able to back up all of these names.
像这个  米格尔·萨尔塞多
Like this one. Miguel Salcedo.
煽动阴谋  他是爆炸案的从犯  对吧
Seditious conspiracy? Accessory to bombings, wasn't he?
他是一位激进的教授
He was an activist professor--
激进分子  是  暴力革命  的委婉说法吗
"Activist" being a euphemism for "violent revolutionary"?
他主张波多黎各独立  是的  他是一个非暴力的怀疑者
He advocated independence for Puerto Rico, and, yes, he was a nonviolent skeptic,
但联邦调查局判处他70年监禁
but the feds sentenced him to 70 years.
这是20世纪80年代杀人犯的六倍
That's six times what a murderer got in the 1980s.
有人死亡
People died.
不按照甘地的模式行事不算犯罪
Not being in the mold of Gandhi isn't a crime.
- 所以  这是一个言论自由的问题  - 没错
- So, this is a free speech issue. - Exactly.
那么说
Then say that.
宪法保护  这是你可以使用的另一个术语
"Constitutionally protected," that's another term you can use.
- 他还在名单上吗  - 暂时
- So he stays on the list? - For now.
但这会让一些人感到不安  你需要磨练你的防守技巧
But this is gonna rattle some cages. You need to hone your defense chops.
我不会是你最后一个要把这个案子交给的人
I am not gonna be the last person you're gonna have to make this case to.
我一直在给斯蒂芬妮打电话发短信  没有回应
I've been calling and texting Stephanie. No response.
发短信还有打电话吗
Texting and calling?
- 不好吗  - 不太好
- Not good? - Not so much.
我捐精出去的孩子跟我玩失踪了
Ghosted by my sperm child.
这称谓叫的真亲切啊
What a touching term of endearment.
我这样想她的时候  就不那么痛苦了
When I think of her that way, it hurts less.
也许给她一个挂坠盒有点过了
Maybe giving her a locket was a little overwhelming.
我的意思是  即使是有着传统家庭背景的年轻女性
I just mean, even young women with conventional parentage
对事物也有复杂的感情  所以给她一些空间吧
have complicated feelings about things, so just give her some space.
这都是你的错
This is all your fault.
好吧  轮到我了
Okay, my turn.
今天早上我和妈妈谈过了  她现在住院了
I spoke to my mom this morning, and she's in the hospital.
- 她会没事吗  - 希望如此
- Is she gonna be okay? - I hope so.
她从来不想把自己当作负担  这让我感到压力
She never wants to feel like a burden, which makes me feel burdened.
我只是  我觉得自己像个糟透的女儿
And I just... I feel like a horrible daughter.
你是个好女儿
You're a wonderful daughter.
在这场无所不包的总统竞选中
You're also an irreplaceable senior staffer
你也是一位不可替代的高级职员
on an all-encompassing presidential campaign.
- 你已经尽力了  - 谢谢你
- You're doing the best you can. - Thank you.
- 但没有人是不可替代的  - 没错
- But no one is irreplaceable. - You are.
现在请不要让我哭
Please don't make me cry right now.
下午三点  你和国家经济委员会有一份经济简报
3:00 p.m., you have an economic brief with the NEC.
然后  你们最后的辩论准备
And then, your final debate prep.
每次我认为辩论不会比准备辩论更糟时
Every time I think the debate can't be worse than the debate prep,
我就想  哦  天哪  当然会
I think, "Oh, God, of course it can."
你一向都是顺风顺水的  我不担心
You have a habit of landing on your feet. I am not worried.
顺便说一下  我一直在研究
By the way, I've been doing research
毒品合法化项目
about drug decriminalization programs.
在葡萄牙  药物滥用现在被当作一个医疗问题来对待
In Portugal, substance abuse is now being treated as a medical problem.
使用海洛因的人数减少了一半
The number of people using heroin has been cut in half.
毒品导致的死亡率比欧洲任何地方都低五倍
The drug-induced death rate is five times lower than anywhere in Europe.
- 怎么做  - 用户会收到一份引证
- How? - Users receive a citation
然后进入一个劝阻小组
and go before a dissuasion panel.
最终  政府为他们提供了支持
Ultimately, the government provides them with support,
而不是监禁或羞辱
not imprisonment or shame.
我明白为什么这对你很重要  你所经历的一切
I understand why this is important to you, with everything you're going through.
在我们的农村社区  人们最关心的是经济和吸毒问题
In our rural communities, the top concerns are economics and drug addiction.
以这一成功为模型的政策变化可能会改变游戏规则
A policy change modeled after this proven success could be a game-changer.
你可以提供一些东西
You could provide something
让无数人遭受这个问题的痛苦
that would give countless people suffering with this problem
不只是希望  而是真正的机会
not just hope, but an actual chance.
跟我说说
Educate me.
成立一个工作组  然后给我一份报告  一个计划
Put together a working group and get back to me with a report, a plan.
如果那时我仍然是总统  我们将讨论实施
And if at that time I'm still president, then we'll talk about implementation.
- 谢谢你  总统先生  - 谢谢你  玛尔斯
- Thank you, Mr. President. - Thank you, Mars.
各位下午好
Good afternoon, everybody.
总统辩论即将开始  我没有新的通知
With the presidential debate coming up, I have no new announcements.
所以  我将回答你们的问题  菲利普
So, I will take your questions. Philip.
柯克曼总统对发布已故
Does President Kirkman have any response
第一夫人车祸照片有何回应吗
to the release of the photos of the late First Lady's car accident?
伙计们  我们不讨论这个问题  好吗  杰米
Guys, we're not addressing this, okay? Jamie.
针对这些事件  总统计划恢复治疗吗
Does the president plan to resume therapy in light of these events?
拜托  大伙  你们必须问点实际的问题  对吧
Come on, guys. You have to ask actual questions, right?
关于真正的新闻  一定有真正的问题  丹尼斯
There must be real questions about real news. Dennis.
柯克曼总统对这些
Does President Kirkman feel any responsibility
阴谋论有什么责任吗
for these conspiracy theories?
你应该为自己感到羞耻  你们所有的人
You should be ashamed of yourself. All of you.
这场报道完全无稽之谈
This story is 100% trash.
这是一个充斥着道德败坏
This is fever-swamp clickbait
和阴谋破坏工作的狂热点击诱饵
for moral degenerates and conspiracy whack jobs.
我相信不管是谁制造了这一切  谢谢你成为他或她的同谋来
I'm sure whoever created this filth thanks you for being his or her accomplice
大肆宣扬这种令人作呕的亵渎行为
in trumpeting this revolting desecration.
基本准则到底怎么了  道德实践到底怎么了
Whatever happened to standards? What happened to ethical practices?
你们有没有想过总统家的孩子
What happened for concern for the First Children?
大伙  那是他们的妈妈  这是他的妻子
Guys, that's their mother! That's his wife!
我希望你们都不会看到你们所爱的人
I hope none of you ever has to see your loved one's remains
的遗体被世界各地的媒体展示
showcased by every media outlet around the world,
然后向你的孩子们解释这些人的想法
and then have to explain to your children
他们应该知道得更多
what these people, who should know better, were thinking.
这不是新闻
This isn't journalism!
我感到作呕
I am so disgusted.
柯克曼总统很反感
President Kirkman is disgusted.
你们开心了
Are you happy?
这就是你们的答案  我们厌恶
There's your answer. We're disgusted...
你们中的每个人
with every single one of you.
写下来
Write that.
跟你女朋友讲点道理
Just talk some sense into your girlfriend.
不  不是这样的
No, that's not how it works.
无论如何  政府不能把
Well, however it works,
米格尔·萨尔塞多包括在这轮赦免中
the administration can't include Miguel Salcedo in this round of pardons.
从现在到投票结束  莫斯将把他塑造成
Moss would make him out to be
拉美裔的奥萨马·本·拉登
the Latino Osama bin Laden from now until the polls close.
我可以和总统谈谈
I can talk to the president.
亲爱的  我可以和总统谈
Honey, I can talk to the president.
我们必须在阻断后路  指的是伊莎贝尔
We need to cut this off at the pass, and that means Isabel.
别让她成为我们失败的原因
Don't let her be the reason that we lose.
什么也别说  的哪一部分你没听懂吗
Which part of "say nothing" didn't you understand?
我给了明确的指示不要回应
I gave specific instructions not to respond,
而你却在那唱那该死的咏叹调吗
and you sing a goddamn aria?
对不起  先生  他们一直在紧逼  我混乱了
I apologize, sir. They just kept pushing, and I lost it.
他们的工作就是推动它  而你的任务就是防守住
Their job is to push it. Yours is to not lose it.
你的工作是保护这届政府  尤其是我的家人
Your job is to protect this administration and, above all, my family!
相反  你把这个报道又播了三天
Instead, you gave the story three more days of airplay
因为你无法控制自己的情绪
because you couldn't control your emotions.
因为一些与你无关的事情
Over something that didn't even concern you.
我绝对没有冒犯的意思
I meant no disrespect.
不用再说了
We're done here.
你为什么不休息几天呢  给他时间冷静下来
Why don't you take a few days? Give him time to cool off.
你是说不来上班吗  我说的都是真的
You mean not come to work? Hey, everything I said there was true.
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
你不能代表总统的时候放任自己的情绪
You don't get to indulge your anger on the president's behalf.
回家  趁你还有工作要做的时候好好想想
Go home, reflect on it while you still have a job to come back to.
柯克曼总统声称他不是政治家
President Kirkman claims he's not a politician.
由于他已任职两年多
Since he's served in office for over two years
没有取得重大成就  我倾向于同意
without a major accomplishment, I'm inclined to agree.
我要向波特先生指出
I would note to Mr. Porter that presiding
主持联邦政府的全面重建
over the complete reconstruction of the federal government
可能被认为是一项成就
might be considered an accomplishment.
我感谢总统的服务
I thank the president for his service,
但头衔是  总司令  而不是  看守总司令
but the title is "commander in chief," not "caretaker in chief."
是时候把我们的最高职位还给一个更有资格的人了
It is time to return our highest office to someone more plainly qualified.
前总统莫斯在妻子去世后拒绝再次参选
Former president Moss declined to run again
他把国家放在首位
after the traumatic passing of his wife, putting country first.
柯克曼总统面临着类似的悲剧
President Kirkman, faced with a similar tragedy,
表现出充分的精神不稳定
exhibited sufficient mental instability
以至于他的副总统要求弹劾他
that his own vice president sought his impeachment.
在那段难以置信的困难时期  我接受了心理咨询
I received counseling during that incredibly difficult time.
不幸的是  我的对手利用我个人的悲痛谋取政治利益
Unfortunately, my opponents used my personal grief for political gain.
总统的联络官  也就是总统的发言人
The intemperate outburst today by the president's communications director,
今天的失控爆发很难指向情感平衡
who speaks for the president, hardly points to emotional equilibrium.
好了  够了  到底怎么回事
Okay, enough! What the hell is going on?
这完全是在浪费我的时间
This is a complete waste of my time!
你们有机会利用这个练习来帮助我
You had an opportunity to use this exercise
磨练和阐明我对真正政治问题的看法
to help me hone and articulate my views on real political issues.
相反  你们选择说这些琐碎的具有人身攻击
Instead, you've chosen to make this about petty, personal attacks
的扯淡的话  我说完了
that are bullshit. I am done.
谢谢你们俩  这种爆发是绝对不能发生的
Thank you both. That outburst is exactly what can't happen.
你不能把愤怒的柯克曼带到辩论中来
You cannot bring Angry Kirkman to the debate.
你的对手想让国情咨文垮台的悲剧重演
Your opponents want a repeat of the State of the Union meltdown.
如果你那样做  我们就输了  就是这么简单
If you do that, we lose. It's as simple as that.
当他们向你出击时  你必须躲避
When they poke, you must pivot.
我不是那种需要被骗上一堂课的孩子
I'm not a child that needs to be tricked into a lesson.
别再对我这样做了
Don't ever do this to me again.
我的工作是让他做好准备
My job is to prepare him.
他可能会生我的气  甚至会抓住不放
He can be so mad at me that he spits nails,
只要他明天不带着这种状态上台
as long as he doesn't carry that energy on to the stage tomorrow.
在这里  那是谁
Right there. Who is that?
- 他在这工作吗  - 我不这么认为
- Does he work here? - I don't think so.
继续放
Keep running it.
他故意掩面  我们得看看他的脸
He's deliberately hiding his face. We need to see his face.
你能换个角度吗
Can you pull up another angle?
看来我们的护士是从多伦多来的  帮我把屏幕放大
Looks like we got our nurse from Toronto. Zoom in on that plate for me.
嘿  戴安娜  我们发现反叛护士了  伊利诺斯州牌照
Hey, Dianne. We got a hit on our rogue nurse. Illinois plates.
EC215LC
Echo-Charlie-Two-One-Five-Lima-Charlie.
我得走了
I have to go.
也要在床头柜上留点钱吗
Wham-bam. Gonna leave some money on the nightstand, too?
事情是  如果你一定要知道  今天早上不太好
Things were... not great this morning, if you must know.
如果我一定要知道吗
If I must know?
我知道你不喜欢我讨论家里的事情
I know you don't like it when I talk about home.
我不太喜欢你不跟我说话
Well, I like it less when you don't talk to me at all,
现在这种事越来越多了
which is happening more and more these days.
我是在这里浪费时间吗
Am I wasting my time here?
你带酒来  操我  然后离开
You bring wine, you fuck me, you leave.
今晚就别这样了  求你了  我有很多事情要做
Let's not do this tonight, please. I got a lot going on.
你总是有很多事情要做
You always have a lot going on.
- 会离开你的妻子吗  玛尔斯  - 这话从何说起
- Are you ever gonna leave your wife, Mars? - Where did that come from?
我是你的情妇  剧本不就是这么写的吗
I'm your mistress. It's in the handbook.
我从没答应过
I never promised that.
不  你一直很小心  天知道
No, you've been nothing if not careful, God knows.
- 我不能离开林恩  - 现在还是永远
- I can't leave Lynn. - Right now or ever?
我真的得走了
I've got to go.
这令人愉快  我们可以下次再谈
This was lovely. We can talk all about this next time.
我不知道有多少次下次了
I don't know how many next times I've got left in me.
如果我想做二奶  我会和我的前任呆在一起
If I wanted to play second fiddle, I would've stayed with my ex.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
但你一开始就知道我的处境
But you knew my situation when this began.
是的  你说得很清楚
Yes, you were clear.
我本不以为然  至少我接受了
And I was okay with it, or I accepted it, at least.
都是因为我
That's on me.
这越来越让人无法忍受
This is becoming unbearable.
你要么想留在这里  要么去那里
You either wanna be here or you wanna be there.
在你两边跑的时候  时间在一分一秒地流逝
The clock's ticking on your having it both ways.
辩论准备伏击的事我很抱歉
Sorry about the debate prep ambush.
洛林可能是个迟钝的人  但我知道她为什么那样做
Lorraine can be a blunt instrument, but I know why she did it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
莫斯是这方面的老手  而我不是
Moss is an old hand at this, and I am not.
你觉得这件事怎么样
How are you feeling about it?
快要吓傻了
Scared shitless.
你最担心什么
What concerns you most?
如何把我的策略变成合适的言论  不想有任何失言
How to turn my policies into soundbites. Not wanting to make any gaffes.
想要听起来很自然而不是很鲁莽的
Wanting to be spontaneous without being reckless.
我尽力把他们都记在我的脑子里
I'm trying to keep that all in my head
盯着一个不停止滴答作响的时钟
while staring straight down a clock that doesn't stop ticking,
知道有一个亿的人在看着
knowing that 100 million people are watching,
评判着我的每一滴汗水  眉毛的每一次皱起  嘴角的每一次抽搐
judging every bead of sweat, furrowed brow, twitch of the lip.
这就是全部了吗
Is that all?
莫斯一生都在为此排练
Moss has been rehearsing for this his whole life.
波特不是这样的  他是一个商人  不是一个政治家
Not Porter. He's a businessman, not a political pro.
这让我想起了那个老笑话
That reminds me of the old joke.
当一个熊向你袭来时你该怎么做
What do you do when a bear charges you?
不要惊慌  你不需要跑得过熊
Don't panic. You don't have to outrun the bear,
你只要比你旁边的人跑得快就行
just the guy standing next to you.
你又不是一个演员  所以不要去演戏
You're not a performer, so don't perform.
继续向选民展示你真实的样子就行
Just keep showing the voters who you really are,
剩下的事自然都会得到解决的
and the rest'll take care of itself.
无论如何我们对这场辩论讨论得够多了  你来是想和我说什么
Anyways, enough about the debate. What did you wanna talk to me about?
我妈妈又住院了
My mother's in the hospital again.
噢  艾米丽  听到这个我很难过
Oh, Emily, I am so sorry.
我今晚要去看她
I'm leaving tonight to see her,
我不是很确定自己将要面对什么  所以
and I'm not exactly sure what I'll be walking into, so...
她会尽全力并且会保护你的
She's gonna try and protect you.
无论如何我想让你知道这个情况
anyway I just wanted to let you know
以防我不能及时赶回来参加这场辩论
in case I don't make it in time for the debate.
别再犹豫了  去陪着你的母亲吧
Don't give it a second thought. Go be with your mother.
直到你真正经历了那种失去
Until you've experienced that kind of loss,
你才能明白死亡的深意
it's impossible to know the depth of its finality.
谢谢你  长官
Thank you, sir.
艾米丽
Emily...
过来
come here.
- 祝你好运  - 你也是
- Good luck. - You, too.
你知道我们应该做什么吗
You know what we should do?
我们就应该辞去我们的工作  开一间酒吧  你觉得怎么样
We should just quit our jobs, open up a bistro. What do you think?
咱俩中可能得有一个先学会怎么做饭
One of us would probably have to learn how to cook first.
胡说  我妈妈在我还没炉子高的时候就教会了我怎么做饭
Shoot, my mama taught me how to cook before I could barely see over the stove.
你知道的  热水玉米面包  牛小排  绿甘蓝
You know, hot water corn bread, short ribs, collard greens.
我甚至能教你一些呢
I might even teach you a little something-something.
怎么了
What's the matter?
有件事我们需要谈一谈了
There's something we should talk about.
说吧
So?
我是
I'm...
未检测出的
undetectable.
你是说  你还没出柜吗
Like, you're on the DL?
不是
No.
我是艾滋病阳性携带者
I'm HIV positive.
我没有把你置于危险中
I never put you at risk.
我们用了避孕套  我们那次是安全的
We used a condom. We were careful.
为什么你不在我们上床前和我说你是艾滋病阳性携带者
Why wouldn't you tell me that you were HIV positive before we had sex?
我不想吓到你
I didn't wanna scare you off.
我知道这听起来欠扁极了
I know that might feel fucked up...
但这不应该被当作一件大事
but it doesn't have to be a big thing.
你先是打算不和我明说
You don't get to decide not to be upfront with me
然后装作这不是什么大事
and then just act like it's no big deal.
- 这就是件该死的大事  - 你没事的
- This is a huge fucking deal. - You're okay.
我保证
I promise.
是的  你可不是会这么说么
Yeah, so you say.
好吧  这不公平
Okay, that's not fair.
你真的想和我谈谈这一切中有哪里是公平的吗
You really wanna talk about what's fair in all this?
你剥夺了我选择的权利
You took away my right to choose.
我明白你的感受
I understand how you feel.
不  我不认为你能明白
No, I don't think you do.
因为我现在听了太多了  我没告诉过你  但这不是什么大事
'Cause I'm hearing a whole lot of, "I didn't tell you, but it's no big deal.
你是安全的
You're okay."
而没有一个真正的道歉
Instead of an actual apology.
不  我不是在为我携带艾滋病而道歉  我吃了药
No, I'm not apologizing for having HIV. I take my meds.
在我很好地治疗了自己的病情后  我确定你没感染
By taking care of myself, I made sure you wouldn't catch it.
为一晚的旅行带两件套装吗
Two suits for an overnight trip?
带多了总比带少了甚至不带要好
Better too many than too few, or nothing at all.
哦  明早我就随便带一件吧
Oh, I'll toss something in a bag in the morning.
我听说你把米格尔·萨尔塞多放在你的赦免名单里了
So, I hear you have Miguel Salcedo on your pardon list.
你真的认为这是一个合适的时候吗
You really think it's the right time?
是洛林让你这么问的吗
Lorraine put you up to this?
当然是她  并且你同意了
Of course she did, and you let her.
这事和洛林无关
This isn't about Lorraine,
这与是否会连累竞选有关
this is about becoming a liability to the campaign.
你是说我将会是一个拖累
You mean me becoming a liability.
哇  亚伦  没人能料到
Wow, Aaron. No one would guess
她能这么操纵你  让你说她想说的话
that she's got her hand up your ass, moving your mouth.
你就没想过我是出于原则才不同意赦免的
Has it ever occurred to you that I might disagree on the pardon on principle?
我的意思是  这个男人夺走了别人的生命  可能会被效仿
I mean, the man inspired an action that took lives.
你不能就这样抹去这个事实
You can't just erase that.
他被起诉是因为他是一个发表不受欢迎言论的棕色皮肤人种
His indictment was based on him being a brown man with unpopular rhetoric.
伊莎  鼓吹炸弹袭击可不止是不受欢迎的  这是会妨碍社会治安的
Agitating for bomb-throwing isn't unpopular, Isi. It's seditious.
米格尔拥有和其他人一样的第一修正案权利
Miguel has First Amendment rights like anyone else.
言论自由不是绝对自由  你知道的
Free speech is not an absolute. You know that.
你不能向一个有那么多人的剧院开火
You can't shout fire in a crowded theater.
你知道这不是一回事  对吗
You know that's not a thing, right?
你在说什么啊  当然是一回事
What are you talking about? Of course it is.
不  和我约会的那个宪事律师不会这样说的
No, not according to a constitutional lawyer I dated.
好吧  那就让我们引用你前男友反对
Well, let's by all means take your old boyfriend's words
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
奥利弗·温德尔·霍姆斯的话
against Oliver Wendell Holmes'.
霍姆斯的意见是被最高法院推翻的
Holmes' opinion was overturned by the Supreme Court.
为了打破法律界限  言论必须去鼓动  即将到来的违法行动
To break the law, speech has to incite "imminent lawless action."
你那激情的前任就是这么说的
Says your ex-flame.
听着  你有一系列合适的名单可以去做那该死的赦免
Look, you have an entire suitable list of fucking pardons.
为什么你要不顾一切地为他冒险
Why'd you have to risk it all for him?
因为这是正确的
Because it's right!
在十二月之前这不能是一件正确的事
It's not gonna be any less right in December.
在那之前他可能就死了
He could be dead by then.
我们整个团队可能会因此玩儿完
We could be packing up our offices!
你还不明白你把总统置于何种境地了吗  或者把我
Do you not understand the position you're putting the president in? Or me?
你现在还能坐在那儿的唯一原因
The only reason why you even have a seat at the table right now
就是我在竞选副主席
is because I'm running for VP.
这可太符合你的一贯作风了
This is so typical.
你总认为你的工作比我的重要
You always think that your work is more important than mine.
因为事实就是如此
That's because it is.
你知道吗  亚伦
You know what, Aaron?
明天你就再找一个拉丁裔做你身边的女伴吧
Find yourself another Latina to be your arm candy tomorrow.
我将忙着做我这无关紧要的工作
I'll be busy doing my insignificant work!
这是怎么了
What's this?
我们好久没亲密了  这是我的错
We haven't been intimate in a while, which is my fault.
但是我现在感觉好点儿了
But I'm feeling better,
而且我想今晚就是一个合适的时机
and I thought tonight could be the night.
多么好的一个惊喜呀
What a nice surprise.
你知道  很多男人都这样
You know... it happens to a lot of men.
我这个年龄的吗
My age?
没必要有任何尴尬
There's no need to be... anything embarrassed about.
我没有
I'm not.
你仍然爱我吗
Do you still love me?
我当然爱你了
Of course I do.
你只是不再被我吸引了  对吗
You're just not attracted to me anymore?
别这样说  甚至别这样想
Don't say that. Don't even think that.
今天忙了一天
It's been a long day.
我累了
I'm tired.
当然
Of course.
俄间谍第一夫人被杀
与敌共眠      杀手柯克曼
白宫中的暗流涌动
莫斯如何带领美国重塑辉煌
马尔斯已经和我说了米格尔·萨尔塞多的事了
Mars has already spoken to me about Miguel Salcedo,
并且我必须坦诚地说  我有我的顾虑
and I have to be honest, I have my concerns.
但他想让我听听你要说的
But he wanted me to hear you out.
还没有任何一个确凿的证据表明
There was never a single piece of hard evidence presented
是他谋划的  或是参与了合谋  甚至不能证明他私下里认识这些投放炸弹的人
that he plotted, or conspired with, or even personally knew the bombers.
但是他被起诉了  被认为犯有共谋暴乱罪
Yet he was charged and found guilty of seditious conspiracy,
并在联邦监狱被判处70年徒刑
and sentenced to 70 years in a federal prison.
这个刑期可是当时已定罪凶手平均刑期的六倍啊
That's six times the average sentence for a convicted murderer at the time.
他的言论煽动了暴行  人们死了
His words incited violence. People died.
那都是气话
They were angry words,
他觉得这些话与他所看到的不公正相称
which he felt were commensurate with the injustices he saw.
并且那些话也鼓励了儿童早餐计划
And those same words also inspired breakfast programs for children,
社区倡议和经济适用房计划
community initiatives and affordable housing.
每个人都应该有言论自由的权利  不仅仅是大多数人
Free speech has to be for everyone, not just the majority.
否则  那就不是自由的或是受到保护的言论了
Otherwise, it's not free or protected speech.
是受到限制的言论  州政府没权利这样做
It's sanctioned speech. And the state has no business enforcing it.
说得好  先生
Well put, sir.
选举是充满政治色彩的时期
Elections are highly-charged political times.
没有办法忽视这一点  这是一个必须考虑的现实
There's no way to ignore that. It's a reality that has to be factored in.
在选举之后  无论输赢  我都可以赦免他
Having said that, win or lose, after the election, I could pardon him.
他是一个即将死去的86岁的人
Well, he's an 86-year-old man in declining health.
接下来的八个星期对他仅有的剩余
The next eight weeks are not inconsequential
生命来讲不是这么无关紧要的
to whatever time he might have left.
- 谢谢你  伊莎贝尔  - 谢谢你  总统先生
- Thank you, Isabel. - Thank you, Mr. President.
- 伊莎贝尔呢  - 她没来
- Where's Isabel? - She's not coming.
为什么她没来呢
Why not?
因为你  我们俩就萨尔塞多的赦免案发生了激烈的争吵
We got in a huge fight over the Salcedo pardon, thanks to you.
为什么是因为我
Why thanks to me?
是你劝说我去和她讲道理的
You're the one who persuaded me to talk sense into her.
我没让你这么做成这样
I didn't say to do it badly.
从现在起  别把我的私生活牵扯进来  好吗
Just from now on, leave my personal life out of this, okay?
你不能有私生活  你还没明白吗
You don't have a personal life. Aren't you getting that?
你们俩可是作为美国甜蜜恋人来参与票选的
You two are polling as America's sweethearts.
我不是说这就值二十多张选票
I'm not saying that's worth two dozen electoral votes,
但是也不能忽视
but it's not negligible either.
你赶紧去给个甜枣挽回她  越快越好
You gotta kiss and make up. The sooner the better.
最好在去西南和加利福尼亚之前挽回她
It'd be best to have her on the swing through the Southwest and California.
妈妈
Mom.
亲爱的  你来啦
Sweetheart, you came.
嗨
Hi.
你觉得怎么样
How are you feeling?
比我看上去要好得多
Better than I look.
这次不仅仅是血栓的问题  是吗
This isn't just a blood clot, is it?
你吃过饭了吗
Have you eaten?
妈妈  请告诉我到底怎么样了
Mom. Please tell me what's going on.
癌症扩散了
The cancer has spread.
我就知道
I knew it.
我要停止化疗了
And I'm stopping the chemo.
不  妈妈  你不能停止化疗
No, Mom. You can't stop.
医生说这由我选择
The doctor said it was my choice.
还有多长时间
How long?
他们猜我的生命还剩下几个月吧  他们也不知道
Months, they think. They don't know.
我需要你帮我做些事
I need you to do something for me.
你说
Anything you want.
我需要你帮我准备一个分类包
I need you to make me a go-pack.
去做
A go...
里面放上各种各样的药  当是时间了我就服下
That's a mixture of pills I can take when it's time.
什么时间啊
When it's time?
对我来说要走的时候
For me to go.
那就是你说的你其他的计划吗
That's what you meant by you had other plans?
你想让我协助你自杀
You're considering assisted suicide?
不可能的  我不会那么做的  那真的是
No, I won't do that. That's...
那是我想要的
It's what I want.
我就呆在这里我们得谈谈这个
I'm gonna stay here and we are gonna talk about this.
不
No.
我现在想要睡觉了
I'm going to go back to sleep now.
- 你也得去辩论会了  -不  妈妈  我不去了
- And you're gonna go to the debate. -No, Mom. No.
我哪都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你去辩论会然后明天再来看我
You go to the debate and come back tomorrow.
我会有一个清单写着我需要你帮我拿到的药
I will have a list of what I need you to get.
就这个
This is it.
这就是那个出现在视频里的车
There's the car from the video.
没错
Yeah.
我们现在要进去吗
Are we going in?
等戴安娜打电话来说拿到搜查令才行
We're waiting for Dianne to call with the warrant.
所以  我们就在这监视着吗
So, this is a stakeout?
刚刚真应该停下来去买点零食
We should've stopped for snacks.
藜麦薯条之类的
Quinoa chips, something.
- 我猜我们只能安静的坐着了  - 好主意
- Guess we'll just sit in silence. - What a great idea.
你一定能胜任的
You look the part.
我知道这将改变我们的所有
I know this is gonna change everything for us,
但是我不得不这样做
but I have to do it.
如果我不这么做  就会
If I don't, then...
我必须得这么做
I just have to.
你站在我这边吗
You still on my side?
我一直在你这边  总统先生
I'm always on your side... Mr. President.
准备好了吗
Ready?
开始吧
Let's do this.
你难道不是应该在奥兰多吗  白马王子
Aren't you supposed to be in Orlando, Prince Charming?
是啊  在我精神病发作后
Yeah, well, after my psychotic episode,
我被建议休息几天
I was encouraged to take a couple days off.
你呢  你难道不是应该在艾伦的辩论会上吗
What about you? Aren't you supposed to be at Aaron's debate?
去不了  我得工作啊
No, 'cause I have a job.
你们俩肯定吵架了
You guys got into a fight.
你得喝点
You need a drink.
来了
Here we go.
今晚的辩论将会由六个环节组成  每个环节十五分钟
Tonight's debate will consist of six 15-minute segments.
然后将会由对第一个问题的两分钟问答时间
There will be two-minute answers to the first question...
看谁都快要迟到了
Look who's almost not late.
来了啊
Hey.
波特先生开始了第一个问题
Mr. Porter got the first question.
- 你还好吗  - 还行
- Are you all right? - I'm fine.
关于在这个国家愈合人种分裂你有什么想法
What is your vision for healing racial divisions in this country?
我希望有一天我们能生活在无所谓人种的国家
My hope is that one day we will live in a color-blind country...
无谓人种根本不可能
Color-blindness isn't a thing!
这个国家的每个人都能得到他们应得的机会
...where every person is given the opportunities they deserve.
我相信要的是真正的公平  而不是正面的区别对待
I believe in true fairness, not positive discrimination.
各科成绩均满分的白人孩子是不可能收到大学的拒信
The white student with a 4.0 GPA should not be denied college admission
为什么要单纯的为了满足一些死板的配额政策
simply because a minority student with lower grades
那些成绩不高的少数种群学生就能被录取
needs to be accepted in order to meet some arbitrary quota.
现在  拿科尔曼总统举个例子
Now, you take President Kirkman, for instance.
为什么呢  他如果当年被康奈尔大学拒了 今天他就不会站在这里
Why, he wouldn't be standing here today if he'd been rejected from Cornell.
女士们先生们  别让莫斯总统欺骗了你
Ladies and gentlemen, do not let President Moss fool you.
这种被有特权和权利的人提出的观点已经很长时间了
This has been the argument made by men of privilege and power for far too long.
没有任何的证据可以表面
There is absolutely no evidence that supports the claim
非裔美国人  拉丁人  亚洲的学生
that African American, Latino or Asian students
正在阻止白人学生去向好学校
are preventing white students from going to school.
至于你的想法  总统先生
And for your own edification, Mr. President,
我为我的时间和我能受到的教育
as grateful as I am for my time and education
即被康奈尔录取倍受感激  但康奈尔其实不是我的第一志愿
that I received from Cornell, Cornell was not my first choice.
事实上  大部分的美国学生
The truth is most American students
都不会选择去他们的第一志愿学校
are not accepted to their first choice of college.
这是一个很简单的算数
It's simple math.
现在如果你想要知道什么才是我所认为的真正的不公平之处
Now, if you wanna understand what I think is truly unfair,
就是高等教育的成本上升
it's the rising cost of higher education.
掠夺性贷款让学生们背负着很大的债务压力
Predatory loans putting students in such great debt
教育再次成为了专为富人的特权
that education is once again becoming a privilege exclusively for the wealthy.
迈尔斯·李  真佩服他
Myles Lee. I bow down.
你真的是一个真正的奇才和网络大师
You're a true wizard and Net master.
多特·艾维斯  我是为科尔曼的竞选做数据分析
Dontae Evans. I do digital, far less ably, for the Kirkman campaign.
我听说过你  你很有能力  荣幸见到你
I heard of you. You've got skills, man. Pleasure.
我一直在追查第一夫人报道的事儿
I have been goose-chasing that source of that First Lady dump.
不管是谁在幕后操作  那操作起来是真熟练
Whoever's behind that is adept.
你认为是我做的
You think it was me?
你确实有嫌疑
You'd have the chops.
莫斯总统确实委托了一些不靠谱的事  但这确实不是他做的
President Moss has commissioned some sketchy stuff, but this wasn't him.
我得回到那里了
I should get back in there.
告诉你我会怎么做  听到任何风声  我都会告诉你
Tell you what I'll do. I hear any whispers in the wind, I'll let you know.
好的
Cool.
你们中的一些人也许知道这个
Some of you might not know this,
但是科尔曼总统在我第一次选举期间为我游说
but President Kirkman canvassed for me during my first election.
我得到的这个也是一个偶然的机会
...that this was an accidental presidency,
因为他胆怯  优劣悬殊和不确定性太大
that he was daunted, over-matched and unsure.
这就是为什么他邀请我来帮助运转这个国家
That's why he begged me to come in to help run the country.
但是美国不需要一个自我怀疑的领导
But America doesn't need a leader filled with self-doubt.
美国需要力量
America needs strength,
那是我的两个对手都没有的东西
and that's something neither of my opponents possess.
科尔曼总统不愿意在办公室里走敢于冒险的一步
President Kirkman has been reluctant to take bold steps in office,
也许是因为他根本没竞选
possibly because he wasn't elected.
但是女士们先生们  根本没有时间给他犹豫
But ladies and gentlemen, this is no time for the hesitant.
一个政治家所说的犹豫  你我都会认为那是周到
What a politician calls "hesitant," you and I would call "thoughtful."
我举个例子
I'll give you an example.
在今晚早些的时候  在我走出这里之前
Earlier this evening, before I walked out here tonight,
我批准了总统特赦名单
I approved the presidential pardon list,
在这个名单上会有波多黎名族主义者米格尔·萨尔塞多
and on that list will be Puerto Rican nationalist Miguel Salcedo.
我去
Holy shit!
现在  你们中的一些人可能认为那是一个富有争议性的决定
Now, some of you might think of that as a controversial choice.
我向你们保证我竞争对手在现在的竞选时
And I guarantee you my political opponents' campaigns right now
在我说话的时正疯狂的写着攻击性广告
are feverishly composing attack ads as I speak.
但是在仔细的想过后
But after careful consideration,
我得出结论  我只是做了该做的事而已
I came to the conclusion that it was simply the right thing to do.
民意要摇摆了
There go the swing states.
不一定
Not necessarily.
现在  周到的人会不同意  但是  这是因为是想法才是算数的
Now, thoughtful people can disagree, but it's the thinking that counts,
而不是政治上的盘算或是下意识的蛊惑
not political calculations or knee-jerk demagoguery.
这需要诚实  周到和见多识广的思考
It requires honest, thoughtful and well-informed thinking.
这些在以后的时间里我们都会用到的品格
Something we could do with more these days.
现在  米格尔·萨尔塞多被监禁不是因为他做的事
Now, Miguel Salcedo wasn't imprisoned for something he did.
而是因为他说的话
He was imprisoned for what he said.
虽然我可能不同意他说的话
And as much as I might disagree with his words,
第一次的宪法修改是为了保护他有说话的权利
the First Amendment should have protected his absolute right to say them.
现在  我知道你们中很多人阅读过
Now, I know that many of you have read the outrageous conspiracy theories
关于我妻子不适时宜的去世这种骇人听闻的阴谋论
surrounding my wife's untimely death.
就算我认为他们十分卑鄙
And as vile as I might think they are,
就算那对我的孩子造成了伤害
and as hurtful as they've been to my children.
喜欢或不喜欢  他们仍然拥有
like it or not, they, too, represent
一个自由人的权利对他们的发言进行保护
a free people's right to a protected speech.
他要准备怎么讲下面的
Where is he going with this?
话虽如此  你也不必宽恕容忍这个内容
Having said that, you do not have to condone the content.
莫斯总统未能作出任何谴责的观点
President Moss has failed to make any statement of condemnation.
所以  我得问您  先生  你可以告诉我或是美国人民
So, I have to ask you, sir, can you say to me or the American people
你确实否认了这些谎言
that you repudiate those lies,
并且你不希望在这种有着下流交易上活动任何人的投票
and that you do not want the vote of anyone who traffics in such filth?
好吧  这只是一个噱头  一个为同情所做出透明的尝试
Well, this is nothing but a stunt, a transparent attempt for sympathy.
我没有听到他
I didn't hear him say it.
可能他太犹豫了
Maybe he's being hesitant.
他肯定不周到体贴
He most certainly isn't being thoughtful.
女士们先生们  政治不用变得很肮脏
Ladies and gentlemen, politics do not need to be this dirty.
在选举的时候  你可以去证明它
And on election day, you have the power to prove it.
你们自己感觉感觉
You saw it yourselves,
我们的分析也表明科尔曼总统胜利了
but our analytics also indicate a huge victory for President Kirkman.
我是说 他带来了对一个辩论来说 真正实在的热情  诚实和信念
I mean, he brought actual passion and honesty and conviction to a debate.
真新鲜  不是吗
It was refreshing, wasn't it?
现在  如果那是你说我们赢了的开心的脸  那你真需要开心点了
Now, if that's your "yay, we won" face, it needs some work.
我没看见伊莎贝尔
I haven't seen Isabel.
是  我们前面吵了一架
Yeah, we got into an argument.
- 这么糟糕  - 是
- That bad? - Yep.
是对你不能克服的事吗
Things you can't get over?
一切对她来说都是战争  她永远是对的
Everything's a battle with her. She's always gotta be right.
这是我人生中一个重大时刻  她甚至都没有露面
This is a huge moment in my life, and she didn't show up for it.
所以  我不认为我可以克服得了
So, I don't think I can get over that.
无论我们俩之间有多少流言蜚语  洛林都会说我们完美的感情
No matter how many rumors Lorraine spreads about our perfect relationship.
是啊  她会不顾一切让你们成为下一个哈里王子和梅根·马克尔
Yeah, she's hell-bent on making you the next Prince Harry and Meghan Markle.
- 好吧  那多讨人厌  - 是
- Well, it's a pain in my ass. -Mmm.
那你想要什么
What do you want?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我妈妈快要去世了
My mom's dying.
天啊  小艾
Jesus, Em.
她想让我帮她结束她的生命
She's asked me to help her end her life.
我只能委婉的说辞
I can only speak in euphemisms.
我妈妈想让我帮她自杀
My mom has asked me to help her... kill herself.
多谢你倾听我
Thanks again for listening to...
你不用为此谢我  现在不用  以后也不用
You don't have to thank me for that. Now or ever.
好吗  抱一下
All right? Come here.
真抱歉  我不该这么做的
I'm so sorry. I shouldn't have done that.
是我们不应该这么做
We shouldn't...
行吗
All right?
你真是一个神奇的女友  艾伦知道
You're an amazing girlfriend. Does Aaron know that?
我意思是  你真的对我来说很神奇  你甚至都不是我的女友
I mean, you're being amazing to me and you're not even my girlfriend,
而且我根本都没想到我们是朋友
and I didn't even think that we were friends.
我们不是
We're not.
谢谢啦
Thank you.
我去
Shit.
伊莱  起来了  那就是我们要找的人
Eli, wake up. That's our guy.
我们应该跟着他吗
Should we follow him?
不  我们应该利用这个机会看房子里有什么
No, this is our chance to see what's in there.
那逮捕令呢
What about the warrant?
快了  但是现在  我们得靠我们自己进去
It's coming. But in the meantime, we're bootstrapping it.
靠我们自己
"Bootstrapping"?
准确的说  我们知道逮捕令快来了  但是我们得快速出手
Technically, we know the warrant's coming, but we're just gonna get a jump on it.
根据规定时间要比我预期的要长
Following the rules lasted longer than I expected.
我以为中央情报局没有发枪
I thought the CIA didn't issue guns.
你觉得我在这个国家
If you think I'm going in there
会不带枪就进去  你简直疯了吧
in a stand-your-ground state without my gun, you're crazy.
出发吧
Let's go.
嗨  亲爱的
Hey, sweetheart.
总统昨晚做的很好  你一定和那事有很大关系
The president did so well last night. You must have had a lot to do with that.
我可能给他准备了下
I may have prepped him a bit.
过来
Come here.
我知道这对你很难
I know how hard this is for you,
但这是我想要的
but it is what I want.
我和你做个交易
I'll make a deal with you.
你来华盛顿陪我
You come stay with me in DC,
你要是这样做  我们就一起度过这段时间
'cause if you're gonna do this, we do it together.
我考虑一下
I'll think about that.
我看不到有人
I don't see anyone.
我怎么没想到那个
Why didn't I think of that?
跟紧就好
Just stay close.
又是个生物试验室
Great, another biolab.
看看那台电脑你能找到些什么
See what you can find on that computer.
赛斯  我很高兴找到你了
Seth, I'm so glad I found you.
我很抱歉  我知道我不应该在这里
I'm sorry, sir. I know I'm not supposed to be here.
我就来理一些文件
I just came to pick up some paperwork.
放松  这就是你该在的地方
Relax, this is exactly where you're supposed to be.
我欠你一个道歉
I owe you an apology.
但是  我才是搞砸的人
But, sir, I'm the one who screwed up.
你没有做到我要求的
You didn't do what I asked,
但你说了真相  而我很尊敬你的诚实
but you told the truth, and I respect that.
谢谢你
Thank you, sir.
对了  祝贺昨晚的辩论获胜
By the way, congrats on the debate win last night.
恕我不揣冒昧地直说
You really handed Moss his ass on a platter,
你真的把莫斯给羞辱了一番
if I may be so bold.
不得不提  这感觉得真他妈好
I have to say, it felt pretty damn good.
美国人对真实性看的很重
Authenticity goes a long way with the American people.
我都无法分辨我是真的
I can't even tell anymore if I'm being authentic
还是在那做戏
or if I'm performing up there.
但你  你发自内心的辩论
But you, you spoke from your heart,
而且确实说的有理有据
and that really says something.
你是个好男人
You're a good man.
也许你该回家梳洗一番了
Maybe you should go home and freshen up a bit.
你闻起来像肯塔基酿酒厂
You smell like a Kentucky distillery.
是的  我以为不会和你拥抱的  所以
Yeah, I didn't think I was gonna run into you, so...
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
可以
You can talk.
天哪  小伊  就看看我  求求你了
For Christ's sake, Isi, just look at me, please?
你是我一生中最重要的人
You're the most important person in my life,
我不想就因为我混蛋而失去了你
and I don't wanna lose you because I'm an asshole.
你为萨尔塞多做的是对的
What you did for Salcedo was right,
而那些我曾说是错的
and those things I said were wrong.
你说到做到  而这是我有时很难做的事
You walk the talk, and that's something I struggle to do sometimes.
但我比你想象的
But I love you for that,
还要爱你那点
more than you know.
伊莎贝尔  求你了
Isabel, please...
原谅我
forgive me.
求求你了
Please.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
这个克劳福德家伙的用户名是  克拉格
This Crawford guy's username is "Krag."
- 知道什么意思吗  - 不知道
- Any idea what that means? - No.
这是个南非荷兰语  有权利  力量  和美德的意思
It's an Afrikaans word for power, strength or virtue.
嗨  你到底是谁
Hey, who the hell are you?
把枪放下  克劳福德
Put the gun down, Crawford.
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
我们有张你在多伦多诊所里的照片
We got a photo of you at the clinic in Toronto,
和再坦帕的公寓楼里
and at the apartment complex in Tampa.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
如果可以的话  我有个问题
If I may, I have a question.
航空工程师和DNA有他妈的什么关系
What's an aerospace engineer doing fucking around with DNA
还有使人感染流感
and infecting people with the flu?
你们找错人了
You've got the wrong guy.
放下你的枪  让我们来谈谈怎么帮你
Put your gun down. Let's talk about how to help you.
帮我  你们简直一无所知
Help me? You haven't got a fucking clue.
这比我重要的多
This is so much bigger than me.
而你们要是再不住手
And you're not gonna stop--
该死的  汉娜
Shit! Hannah!
Eighty-eight?
这是白人至上主义的象征
It's a white supremacist symbol...
希特勒万岁
for "Heil Hitler."
H  是字母表里的第八个字母
H is the eighth letter of the alphabet.
- 特洛伊  你已经几天躲着我了  - 你声音小点
- Troy. You've been ignoring me for days. - Keep your voice down.
我不会和西翼中这样谈话
I'm not having this conversation in the middle of the West Wing.
进来说
In here.
这在很多层面上都不合适
This is inappropriate on so many levels.
我很抱歉你觉得我好像拿了你什么东西似的
I am sorry you feel like I took something away from you.
或是我撒谎了
Or that I lied.
但不和我说话不能解决任何事
But not speaking to me isn't gonna solve anything.
我只是不知道该怎么面对这事
I just don't know how to deal with this.
我订了这个房间
I booked this room.
菲力克斯  你能就给我们一点时间吗
Can you just give us a minute, Felix?
我看着许多人死在密西西比长大后死去
I watched a lot of men die growing up in Mississippi.
他们看起来都像我
They all looked like me.
他们喜欢和我说话
They talked like me.
他们像我一样去爱
They loved like me.
他们最后得了艾滋病
And they ended up with AIDS.
我发誓那永远不会是我
I swore that would never be me.
我明白
I get that.
但我和你说过  我只是携带者
But I told you, I'm undetectable.
事实上  比起最近还没有真正测试过的人相比
It's actually safer to have sex with someone who is undetectable
与我这样的人做爱更安全
than it is with someone that hasn't really been tested recently.
你上次测试是什么时候
When's the last time you were tested?
大概一年前
About a year ago.
那以后你和多少人勾搭上了
And how many people have you hooked up with since then?
我是攻  风险是不一样的
I'm a top. The risk is different.
我也是从一个攻那里染来的病
The person I got it from was a top.
- 是的  很好  我是干净的  - 而我是脏的
- Yeah, well, I'm clean. - And I'm dirty?
积极并不意味着我不道德
Being positive doesn't mean I am immoral
或者我因为做错事而受到惩罚
or that I'm being punished for doing something wrong.
嗨  告诉我
Hey, tell me...
你总是等到上过了才让别人知道吗
you always wait until after before you let a guy know?
我等是因为我喜欢你
I waited because I liked you,
而事实上我害怕被拒绝
and I was actually afraid of being rejected.
我就觉得我不能信任你
I just feel like I can't trust you.
我们可以在这结束了
We can end this here.
不管这是什么
Whatever this was.
兄弟们
Guys.
房间是你的  我们说完了
The room's yours. We're done.
但丁
Dontae.
林恩  林恩
Lynn? Lynn?
林恩  林恩  林恩  林恩  醒醒
Lynn? Lynn? Lynn, Lynn. Wake up.
林恩  醒醒
Lynn, wake up.
操
Shit!
911.
我现在需要一辆救护车
I need an ambulance right away.
我妻子用药过量了  84号巴里维尔街道
My wife OD'd. 84 Barryville Street.
林恩  撑住  撑住
Come on, Lynn. Stay here. Stay here.
小佩  你为什么看着这些东西  这只会让你难过
Penn, why are you looking at that stuff? It's just gonna make you upset.
你看到过他们怎么说你吗
Have you read what they're saying about you?
我看过
Yes, I have.
- 你怎么不气  - 一开始我挺气的
- Why aren't you mad? - I was, at first.
然后我觉得
And then I realized...
生气解决不了任何事
getting mad wasn't gonna fix anything.
遗憾的是  有时候  当总统意味着
Sadly, sometimes, being president means
人们说些对你说些很尖酸刻薄的话
that people are gonna say mean things about you...
还攻击你爱的人
and about the people that you love.
那你知道怎样让我好受点吗
You know what makes me feel better, though?
我知道真相
I know the truth.
我知道妈妈有多特别  萨沙  里奥还有你
I know how special Mommy was. Sasha, Leo, you.
真相是  我爱你比胜过世间万物
And the truth is, I love you more than anything in the world
这才是最重要的
and that's all that matters.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
书包
Book bag.
还是不知道你怎么能背得动的
I still don't know how you carry that thing.
汤姆·柯克曼  哀悼的丈夫
Tom Kirkman, mourning husband
还是凶残的配偶  你来判断
or murderous spouse? You be the judge.
你的配音是蛋糕上的糖霜
Your voice-over is the icing on the cake.
只需要一点独创性
Ah, all it took was a little ingenuity
- 以及电音  - 是的
- and electronic distortion. - Yeah.
不过  这招确实奏效了  激起了柯克曼的同情者
Sure did the trick, though, stirring up Kirkman sympathizers.
是的  我对莫斯说  操你妈  再好不过了
Oh, yeah. I couldn't have said "fuck you" to Moss any better
如果我把它涂在碧昂斯的旅游巴士旁边
if I'd painted it on the side of Beyonce's tour bus.
我有东西给你
I have something for you.
有些额外的东西用来转移但丁的注意力
There's a little extra in there for diverting Dontae.
如果你还需要什么  请告诉我  莫斯给我付的薪水微薄
Let me know if you need anything else. Moss is paying me in nickels and dimes.
我会保持联系
I'll be in touch.
黛安娜和联邦调查局谈过了
Dianne talked to the FBI.
克劳福德是一个新分公司的负责人
Crawford was the leader of a new branch
新公司  黎明运动  的口号是  复兴我们的国家
of the Rising Dawn movement called "Reclaim Our Nation."
他在招募年轻的专业人士
He was recruiting young professionals.
这是一个新的病态转折  新纳粹主义的博士们
That's a new sick twist. Neo-Nazi PhDs.
另一件让我彻夜难眠的事
Another thing to keep me up all night.
是的  很显然  自从密苏里州的右派集会后
Yeah, well, apparently, the FBI were tracking him
联邦调查局就一直在追踪他
since the alt-right rally in Missouri,
但他们没有任何指控他的罪名
but they didn't have anything to charge him with.
一切都讲得通了
It's all starting to make sense.
对DNA动手脚  制造出一种设计独特的种族生物武器
Tinkering with DNA to make a designer ethnic bioweapon.
该死
Oh, shit.
怎么
What?
鸟
The birds.
那些红雀
The cardinals.
他们用一片剧毒的天花杀死了他们
They killed them with the flu using a virulent piece of smallpox,
然后他们把目标锁定在有色人种身上  让他们患上流感
then they targeted people of color and gave them the flu.
如果他们把这些放在一起
If they put this all together,
你和我以及世上很多人都得死
you and I and a big part of the world are dead.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177